newsinsites.com 2013-05-06

# Privacy Policy - News In Sites

## Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Policy applies to News In Sites and all Websites owned and maintained by Race River Corporation Pty Ltd.

Race River Corporation (Race River) is strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with our products and services and online content of our websites. Our desire is to provide a safe and secure environment for our visitors.

This notice describes the privacy policy of Race River and applies to any sites owned and maintained by us. For existing users of our software, your access and use of our websites may be governed by the terms and conditions of the agreements already entered into with Race River, and may not be subject to this policy.

**Collection of Information**

We collect these types of information through our websites: 

  * Information You Give Us: We store any information you give us, by visiting our websites or any other form of correspondence to respond to your requests and to communicate with you.
  * Automatic Information: We receive and store information whenever you interact with us, direct and through our websites. For example, through "cookies", we obtain information when your web browser accesses our websites.

**Sharing Information**

Race River will not sell your personally identifiable information to others. Race River may share your information with its entities located in other countries and/or business partners in order to help satisfy your business needs. When you register at our sites, we collect the information you provide. Such information is used to improve the content and layout of our Web pages, notify you about product updates and updates to our website, or contacting consumers for sales and marketing purposes. If you supply us with your telephone number online, you may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders you have placed online. You also may receive telephone call from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming upgrades and events.

Our product is sold on a subscription basis and as such will send e-mail notifications as a service to inform you about the status of your account or your orders and new updates. These are essential messages needed to maintain your account and your subscription.

**Compliance with the Law**

We may release account and other personal information to comply with law, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Race River, our users, or others. Such release includes responding to subpoenas, compliance with court orders and legal requests. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit our websites, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy. Please send any concerns you may have about privacy on our websites to the following e-mail address: [info@newsinsites.com](mailto:info@newsinsites.com). Race River Corporation will respond to your request and attempt to resolve any matters that violate Race River policies. Our business constantly changes therefore this Policy may change, and use of information that we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may send periodic reminders of our notices via e-mail, please check our websites frequently for changes.
